what let me in it's just
me
okay so it's bad I'm sorry this is
happening to you on the one night that
jery comes over to my apartment I
explode I mean like this is the worst
this is the best this is a sexy
situation it's terrifying outside it's
candles all lit and who's your
competition Mara bever Abby I'm going to
take care of this for you there's no way
I am a doo ninja what does that even
mean you you do do you grant me
permission to use any means necessary to
make this go away sure fine look me in
the eyes
and tell me I have your
permission you have my permission any
means necessary any means necessary
great awesome now get out there and
bounce some little titties for that
hunky qu Latino and whatever else he is
I don't know okay thank you hey come in
oh my God thank
you
okay oh
Lord
hold
up yeah four and three and two and
[Music]
one